criticalbench.com 2016-05-06

# CriticalBench.com Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

Critical Bench, Inc. has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: Critical Bench LLC, http://www.criticalbench.com 

Cookies 

Your Internet browser has a feature called "cookies" which store small amounts of data on your computer about your visit to Critical Bench. Our site does not currently use cookies however in the future, cookies may be used to deliver content specific to your interest. 

Traffic Data 

Each time a visitor comes to Critical Bench, we collect some basic technical information. We use software to keep track of traffic to our site and acquire such information as the location from which the traffic originates and which particular pages within Critical Bench are being viewed and for how long. We may know for instance, that we had 10,000 hits and 2,000 individual visitors to our Web site today, but we do not know their names, addresses, or other personal information. 

Third Parties 

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

Links 

The Critical Bench Web site contains links to other Web sites. Critical Bench is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

Security 

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Our computer networks and those of our hosting company are protected by passwords, firewalls and other security. 

Is credit card / transaction information secure? 

We care about the safety and security of your transaction. We use SSL (Secure Sockets Layer) to communicate with your browser software when you order from us online and thereby provide us with credit card or similar information. SSL is the industry standard security protocol, which makes it extremely difficult for anyone else to intercept your credit card / transaction and order information that you send us when you submit your online order. We take precautions to safeguard your credit card data in our internal systems. 

Order Forms 

Our site uses an order form for customers to request information, products, and services. We collect contact information (like e-mail address), and financial information (like account or credit card numbers). Contact information from the order forms is used to ship purchases and may be used to send information about our company through the mail. The customer's contact information is also used to get in touch with the customer when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings by visiting www.criticalbench.com/newsletter2.htm or sending a letter to the following postal address: 

_Critical Bench, Inc.  
PO BOX 17959  
Clearwater, FL 33762_

Monthly Newsletter, "The Bench Press" 

Critical Bench offers a periodic e-mail service to those who are interested in hearing about the latest news in the weight lifting and powerlifting industry. "The Bench Press" is strictly opt-in. You will not receive them unless you have voluntary subscribed to the service. If you ever wish to modify your address or unsubscribe, please visit www.criticalbench.com/newsletter2.htm. 

Contacting Critical Bench 

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you may use our feedback form.
